Felipe Brito

Computer Engineer

5598 Ormidale St, Vancouver BC | felipefjbrito@gmail.com | https://github.com/FelipeFJBrito | +1(236)234-2559

SUMMARY

Passionate for developing and integrating new solutions, with over 2 year of experience in software development. Skilled with excellent knowledge of office practices and procedures, database management, and programing skills. Strong team player with excellent time management, and proven ability to multi-task.

EXPERIENCES

IT FIELD TECHNICIAN - KELLY SERVICES CANADA

Feb. 2024 - Present

- Responsable for installation of new equipment, and the efficient relocation of existing equipment to meet client needs with minimal disruption.
- Modified systems, upgraded hardware, and troubleshooted existing hardware by assessing their system requirements, identifying areas for improvement, and implementing necessary modifications and upgrades.
- Worked on larger projects by updating computers and servers for PC systems, as well as handling the installation and setup of printers to seamlessly integrate into existing networks.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER-SMART4

Jun. 2021 - Sep. 2022

- Responsible for developing and maintaining systems for public agencies, utilizing Java for the backend and the ZK framework for frontend development in HTML. My daily tasks involved implementing new features and resolving bugs in these systems.
- Using SQL queries, I managed the databases associated with these systems. Some of my tasks
 included creating new tables, optimizing queries, creating forms, and updating data to
 accommodate new features or system enhancements.
- I utilized Git for version updates. This involved keeping branches updated with the latest modifications as they were completed.
- Maintained, troubleshoot, and managed the use of local area networks (LANs), computer workstations, connections to the Internet and peripheral equipment.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY AREA 1 WYDEN, Salvador, BA **Bachelor of Computer Engineering**, Jan. 2015 – Oct. 2022

LANGARA COLLEGE, Vancouver, BC

Associate of Science: Computer Science, starting May. 2024

LANGUAGES

Portuguese: Native English: Fluent Spanish: Intermediate

SKILLS

- IT Troubleshooting & Problem-solving
- Programming in Python, Java, and Javascript
- Repair and maintenance of computers
- Database development, and manipulation
- SQL
- GIT
- Solving problems in a comperative way